大家别忘了订阅
hey guys don't forget to subscribe and
打开通知，
turn on your notifications mega what's
错，你为什么看上去这么难过？
wrong why are you so sad
那是你知道我妈妈只是
it was that you know what my mom just
有一个新男朋友，我不知道我怎么了
got a new boyfriend I don't know how I'm
喜欢为她担心，她不是那样的人
like worried for her she's not that
年轻
young
哦，拜托，你只是想你的爸爸了。
oh come on you just missed your dad I
想认真上这节课
want to go over this class seriously
我要去的老师好吗？
where is the teacher hi class I'll be
得罪了-今天我的名字是先生。
offended - for today my name is mr.
巴克纳博士霍夫曼今天病了，所以
Buckner dr. Hoffman is out sick today so
他让我进来教课
he had me come in and teach the class
嘿，我说你知道我们去吧
hey I said you know let's go around the
上课，互相了解是的，我
class and learn about each other yes I
是一周的SPE，您可以参加
am a go week SPE and you can take the
最典型的是上课时间可以
bottom on typical it's class time can
你安静点。 Buckner我在Ella上课
you be quiet mr. Buckner I'm class Ella
维多利亚时代，如果您什么都需要
Victorian if you need anything at all
你只是让我知道
you just let me know
谢谢乔茜，我下课后见
Thank You Josie I'll see you after class
他会成为我们的，并且知道你是如此
he's gonna be ours and knows you're so
正确，这是在李中锋比赛中
right it's on Center Lee competition
当我已经赢得生动时
when I've already won vivid
你把老师划好了，让我们
you got teacher zoned okay fine let's
第一个下注让他参加
make a bet the first one to get him to
在脸颊上亲你
kiss you on the cheek hey guys
好的，抱歉，我迟到了，所以规则
okay sorry I'm late alright so the rules
如下没有规则
are as follows there are no rules
你欠我你所有的一切
you owe me you get all of this
哦
Oh
你好吧，哦，是的，不好吧，走吧
you okay oh yes no okay well let's go
让我们打球，我不认识我
let's play ball I don't know I meet up
所有这些热门老师的事情，我和
all this hot teacher thing and me and
切尔西让我感到压力重重
Chelsea just gets me like stressed out
是的，我只是要更具侵略性
and yeah I just gotta be more aggressive
不，你能打我一拳吗
don't ya can you punch her in the face I
会打她的脸
will punch her in the face
谢谢，嘿，莱拉，很酷，我可以
thank you hey Leila that's cool I could
带你四处看看
show you around
我要解决一点，但也许之后
I gotta tackle a little but maybe after
午餐好吧，礼来，也许一分钟的谈话
lunch okay hey Lilly maybe a minute talk
是的，很好，我听到的很多
yes oh okay cool I've heard so much
关于你，我确实想过来
about you and I did want to come over
自我介绍，你知道
and introduce myself and you know that
我可以，是的，来这里好吧，不，我是
one may I yeah come here okay no I'm
我们现在几乎是一家人了，等等我
we're practically family now so wait I'm
和你妈妈约会真是太好了
dating your mom it's been going so great
你是他是枪的家伙
you're the guy he's a gun
爆炸了，你还好吗
it's been a blast are you okay
怎么回事哟，你还好吗
what's going on yo are you okay this
有一个梦，对不起，我只有这些
there's a dream sorry I just have these
我手上有个小小的梦想
little dreams in my hands I okay yeah
完全可以理解的是
totally understandable yeah there's my
妈妈
mom
嘿，性感宝贝，非常感谢你们
hey sexy honey thank you guys so much
看着别忘了喜欢
for watching don't forget to Like
评论并查看我的图像链接
comment and check out my link for image